原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
所以这是你的新事业了
So this is your new business...
现在感觉走对路了
Yeah, this feels about right.
-妈妈  怎么回事  -你注定要成为我的女儿
- Mom, what's happening? - It was your destiny to be my daughter.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
-成为梦想者  -我也必须清除记忆
- To be Dreamer. - I have to be mind-wiped, too.
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
很高兴能帮上忙  艾丽克斯
Happy to help, Alex.
我衷心希望你
I would really appreciate it
能称我为丹弗斯局长
if you would address me as Director Danvers.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
一会见
See you soon.
自由  自由
Liberty! Liberty!
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
警察正在通缉
Police are on the lookout
一对假扮成聚会常客的夫妻
for a couple masquerading as partygoers
他们抢劫了参加
who robbed the attendees at an event
后期     你是不是饿得慌
奥克斯绝壁高端晚会的客人
in an upscale enclave of Oaks Bluff.
现场无人受伤  但是这对夫妻目前带着
No one was harmed but the couple appears to have absconded
总监     你是不是饿得慌
价值几十万美元的珠宝与现金逃逸
with several hundred thousand dollars in jewels and cash.
我们要出名了
We're getting famous.
他们从金·卡戴珊那里偷的戒指跟这个很像
You know the one they stole from Kim K looked just like this.
但是这些手镯比她的卡地亚可棒多了
But these bracelets are way nicer than her Cartiers.
小靓贼  不如你别再欣赏那些珠宝
Hey, Bling Ring. How about you stop admiring the loot
把注意力放在我身上怎样
and start paying attention to me, huh?
逃跑的时候  我眼睛上挨了一拳呢
I'm the one who got the shiner making our getaway.
那是因为你动作太慢了  查科斯特
That's because you're too slow, Chuckster.
总是低估
Always underestimating
有钱人会多么爱惜自己的宝贝
how much rich people like holding on to their stuff.
这是什么
What's this?
假面舞会
情人节
明晚有钱人的舞会  或许又能干一大笔
Rich people's ball tomorrow night. Could be another big score.
你可真是个蠢货
You're a real idiot.
来帮我开下门  帕梅拉  门卡住了
Come around and help me out, Pamela. Door's jammed.
你差点撞上了什么
What the hell did you almost crash us into?
超 女
第四季 第十二集
棉花糖玫瑰可真好吃
Marshmallow roses are so good.
你应该给荣恩留一个的
You should save one of those for J'onn, you know.
这是我的  你想要吗  可好吃了
This one's for me. You want one? They're delicious.
不
No.
情人节快乐啊
Happy Valentine's Day.
太感谢你了
Thank you so much.
我的天啊  这地方太棒了
And, oh, my gosh, this place is awesome.
真不敢相信花了你一周的时间才请我过来
I can't believe it's taken you weeks to finally have me over.
我就是想让你看到之前把这地方都弄好
Well, I just wanted to get the place fully set up before you saw it.
我真为你骄傲
Oh, I am so proud of you.
我看到不只有我们
And I see we're not the only ones
给你送了情人节礼物
who gave you a Valentine's gift.
这大部分是互助小组里的外星人送的
Well, most of these are from the aliens in my support group.
这盒是一个犯罪监护小组的成员送的
This box is from members of a Crime Watch
我帮忙抓捕了一个
I helped set up to catch taggers
在街区里到处涂写
who were spray painting "Free Ben Lockwood"
"释放本·洛克伍德"的混混
Up and down the block.
这些花是我之前帮助找到家人的突曼人送的
And these flowers are from a Toomian whose lost family I found.
你居然已经帮助了这么多人
Well, it is amazing how many clients you've already helped.
我是说  你离开超查部
I mean, you left the DEO
是想要改变你的人生  你做到了
with the goal to change your life, and you have.
我在你的话中听出了不满
I sense discontent in your voice.
和哈雷相处得如何  好点了吗
How are things with Haley? Better?
她一直在华盛顿  所以还算好吧
Um, she's been in Washington, so that's good, I guess.
就是看到你做到了这么多
It's just seeing how much you've accomplished,
提醒了我自己在接手超查部之后的成就太小了
it reminds me of how little I've done since I took over the DEO.
你的成就可不小
You have not done little.
默茜和奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯  自由代表
Mercy and Otis Graves. Agent Liberty.
我是说我的私人生活
I mean in my personal life.
我接手超查部是想用那种稳定性
I took over the DEO to use that stability
来支持我去追求自己想要东西的
to finally be able to pursue the things that I want.
一开始我确实做到了
And I did, you know, at first.
-我有不少约会  -我们知道
- And I dated a lot. - Oh, we know.
是啊
Yeah, well...
我同时还在走收养程序
You know, and I was also working on my adoption portfolio
但是  在马斯丁总统被曝光之后
but, you know, when President Marsdin got exposed,
这一切都被放到了一旁
it kind of all just fell to the wayside.
这事奇怪的就是  我感觉我最近有一种
It's weird because I feel like I have this capacity
能做到更多事情的能力  但是却什么都没成
for so much more lately and I'm doing nothing.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果你真想重出江湖
Well, if you feel like getting back out there,
我知道尼娅和她的室友今晚
I know Nia and her roommate are throwing
要举办一个非常有意思的情人节派对
a very happening Valentine's party tonight.
我们可以一起去  我可以帮你把妹
We could go together. I could be your wing-woman.
为什么这让我感到害怕
Why does that scare me?
等一下
Hold on.
警察发现一辆车
Well, police found a car that apparently crashed
在躲避小行星时撞毁  所以我得走了
trying to avoid an asteroid. So, I'm gonna go.
好  很高兴见到你
Yeah. Good to see you.
我也是
Yeah, you too.
-我爱你们俩  -爱你
- I love you both. - Love you.
现在换你看起来不满了
Now you're looking discontent.
我就是想她了
I just miss her.
当她的叛逆搭档
Being her partner in crime.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在我得赶紧走了
And now I need to get out of here
省得我把你的情人节礼物都吃了
before I eat all your Valentines.
不好意思  你请
Oh. Excuse me. Go ahead.
斯图尔特夫人  很高兴你能找到这里
Uh, Mrs. Stuart. Glad you found the place.
-请坐吧  -谢谢
- Please, have a seat. - Thank you.
今天有什么能帮您的吗
So how can I help you today?
我不知道还能去找谁
I didn't know who else to call.
我想我的丈夫被绑架了
I think my husband's been kidnapped.
-布莱尼  -正是在下
- Brainy? - It is I.
我想先说清楚  鉴于上次就没说清楚
And I'd like to make myself clear, since I did not last time.
我来不是为了约会
I am not here for a date.
也祝你情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day to you, too.
我觉察到了讽刺  这让我感到很不解
I sense sarcasm, which I find confusing in this context.
我来这里
You see, I am here
是因为卡拉告诉我你母亲过世了
because Kara told me about your mother's passing,
我听到之后非常伤心
which I was very sorry to hear.
但做过模拟运算之后
But having run simulations,
我计算出现在有87.4%的几率
I've deduced that there's an 87.4% chance
你会想要成为一名超级英雄
that you would now wish to train as a superhero.
我带来了我最复杂的思维迷宫
And I have brought my most complex mind mazes
来帮助你锻炼技巧和解析梦境
to help you hone your skills and interpret your dreams.
布莱尼  我知道我命中注定会拥有这些能力
Brainy, I know it's my destiny to have these powers.
但我还在哀悼之中  布莱尼
But I'm still grieving, Brainy.
我母亲的过世太突然了
My mother passed away so suddenly.
你有没有想过把你的悲痛放入小盒子之中
Have you ever considered putting your grief into tiny boxes?
听起来不太健康
That doesn't sound very healthy.
也可以是健康的
It could be.
再说  这样你就能解放自己来训练
Besides, then it would free you up to train
然后加入我和超女打击犯罪的大家庭
and then join mine and Supergirl's crime-fighting family.
某天我会很乐意加入你们的大家庭
I would love to join your family someday.
我只是现在还没准备好开始训练
But I'm just not ready to train right now.
好吧  我带上我的思维迷宫走人
Very well. I shall take my mind mazes and go.
布莱尼  布莱尼
Brainy. Brainy.
我室友伊薇特今晚要办一个情人节派对
My roommate Yvette's having a Valentine's party tonight
她想让我打起精神
to try to cheer me up.
你想来吗
If you wanna come?
事实上  我  我很愿意来
Actually, I would... I would love to attend.
太好了
Great.
那就约好了
Then it's a date.
-别愁眉苦脸的  孩子  -为什么
- Don't look so troubled, son. - Why not?
你被关起来了
You're locked up
只有你有足够的勇气
and you're the only one who's brave enough
站出来维护人类
to stand up for humanity.
-这不公平  -我必须相信
-It isn't right. - Listen, the movement that was created,
已经展开的运动能为我的释放创造条件
I have to believe will create the circumstances of my release.
可我现在就想为你做些什么
But... I wanna do something for you now.
那就拿出男人样
Well, then be a man.
拿出行动
A man of action.
成为你爷爷当年希望我成为的那个男人
Be the man that your grandfather wanted me to be,
在你这个年纪就要做到
but at your age.
探访时间结束了
Visiting hours are now over.
我们该走了
We should go.
我们下周再来看你
We'll see you next week.
乔治
Hey, George.
过来
Come here.
哈雷上校  没想到你这么快就回来了
Colonel Haley? I didn't expect to see you so soon.
我提早回来帮我女儿
Yeah, well, I came back early to help my daughter.
-你有女儿  -别这么惊讶  局长
- You have a daughter? - Don't look so surprised, Director.
我在工作之外也有自己的生活
I do have a life outside the service.
她在学校项目上遇到了困难
She was having trouble on a school project
所以我回来帮她
so I came back to help her.
我用热熔胶枪的本事可不一般
You'd be impressed by what I can do with a glue gun.
能和妈妈共度时光她肯定很开心
It must've been nice for her to have some time with her mom.
跟她合作要比在总统办公室那些天
You know, working with her was much more pleasant
愉快多了
than my time at the Oval.
看来进行得不太顺利
I take it that part didn't go over so well.
我没有总统想要的答案
The president wanted answers I couldn't give him
就是关于上次你处理的那些愤怒毒品
about the rage drug you dealt with the other week.
同时令他惊慌的是
He's also dismayed that
本·洛克伍德的得票数比他高
Ben Lockwood is polling better than he is.
这让我们都很惊慌
Well, we're all dismayed by that.
长官  您得看看这个
Ma'am, you need to see this.
北美防空联合司令部把这误报成了小行星
NORAD misidentified this as an asteroid,
可这是某种飞船
but it's some type of ship.
看起来飞船中的生物吃掉了这个人的心脏
And whatever came out of it seems to have eaten this man's heart.
只吃了心脏
And nothing else.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
这个生物似乎完美地取出了他的心脏
It's like the creature extracted his heart perfectly.
只造成了最小组织损伤
There's minimal tissue damage.
没有失血  伤口仿佛自行烧灼了
There's no blood loss. It's like it cauterized itself.
精密的杀人方法
A sophisticated killing.
和它完全伪装成石头的飞船一样精密
Much like its ship, which presented as solid rock.
另一件有趣的事是该生物蜕掉的皮
Also, what's interesting is this creature's shed skin
表明它在到达后不久
suggests it underwent some
就进行了某种变形
sort of metamorphosis quickly after arrival.
这让我很安心
which I do find comforting.
我宁愿面对变形的它而不是蛇形生物
I would much rather face that than anything snake-like,
我对蛇有很深的恐惧
which I do have a deep phobia about.
任何理性的人都有
As any rational being would.
-你讨厌蛇  -是的
- You hate snakes? - Yes.
就像斯皮尔伯格的经典大片
Much like the hero of the Spielberg epic,
《夺宝奇兵》的主角一样
Raiders of the Lost Ark.
很棒的电影
A terrific picture.
无论如何  我分析了该生物表皮的DNA
In any event, I analyzed the DNA from the creature's skin,
并合成了那怪兽现在可能的模样
and made a composite of what the beast might look like now.
刚刚又发现了两名受害者
Two more victims were just discovered.
他们住在飞船降落点一千六百米外的大宅
They lived in a mansion a mile from where that pod landed.
死亡原因一样
Same exact cause of death.
无论杀死这些人的是什么
We need to find whatever killed these people
我们得在大众开始恐慌前找出它
before we have a panic on our hands.
假如我对数据的解读是正确的
If my interpretation of the data is correct,
这就是我们要找的
this is what we're looking for.
这是什么
What is it?
未知生物
Unknown.
我向总统汇报过了  他不希望媒体报道
I've updated the president. He wants this kept out of the press.
人类已经很为自己的安危担忧了
Humans are already feeling so vulnerable.
我们会竭尽所能
We'll do whatever we can.
我几小时后回来  有进展通知我
I'll be back in a few hours. Update me with any progress.
遵命  长官
Yes, ma'am.
我喜欢你的装潢
I love what you've done to the place.
看起来真的有新闻编辑室的样子了
Looks like an actual newsroom now.
是啊  我知道
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
就像《华盛顿邮报》一样
Like The Washington Post.
你怎么突然来了
So what do I owe the surprise?
你离开时来我办公室的那位女士
Uh, well, the lady who came into my office as you were leaving,
她丈夫是外星事务部部长
her husband is the Director of Alien Affairs.
-安东尼·斯图尔特吗  -没错没错
- You mean, Anthony Stuart? - That's right. That's right.
-他帮忙起草了《外星人赦免法》  -对
- He helped draft the Alien Amnesty Act. - Right.
自洛克伍德被囚以来  他和他妻子
He and his wife have been getting a lot of threats
一直收到了许多威胁
ever since Lockwood was imprisoned,
昨晚他没回家
and last night he never made it home.
她认为他被绑架了
She thinks he was kidnapped?
我能想象凯特科对斯图尔特有过许多调查
I imagine CatCo has a lot of research on Stuart.
我希望能给你个独家爆料
I was hoping that I could give you the scoop,
作为回报  你可以帮我进行调查
and in return, you could help with my investigation.
尽管开口  听起来是个重要新闻
Whatever you need. Sounds like it's an important story.
这种事超查部也可能感兴趣
This is something I think the DEO might be interested in, too.
那样的话  从我们今早的谈话来看
And if that's the case, per our conversation this morning,
你不能以超女的身份跟艾丽克斯合作
you can't work with Alex as Supergirl,
但你或许能跟她合力调查这个案子
but maybe you could team up with her on this.
今天是情人节  你来牵红线了
It's Valentine's Day and you're being a matchmaker.
一切还好吗
Everything okay?
你带着大礼物来了能不好吗
Well, now that you're here with a very large present...
我们上次在湖边小屋时  我在清晨拍的
I took this on our last morning at the lake house together.
快请拆开
Open it, please.
当我们远离一切  只有你和我时
This is how I see you when we're away from everything else
这就是我眼中的你
and it's just you and I.
那时一切都很完美
When it's perfect.
我们去巴黎吧
Let's go to Paris.
今晚出发
Tonight.
过一个情人节周末  躲开所有人
For Valentine's weekend, away from everything else.
-你是认真的吗  -你觉得我像开玩笑的人吗
- You're serious? - Have you ever known me to joke?
不像  但是你也不像一个
No. Um, no. But I've never known you
想突然来一场旅行的人
to offer spontaneous trips either.
你确定没出什么事吗
Are you sure everything's okay?
詹姆斯  我们从来没享受过当下
James, we never just live in the moment.
我们应该多活在当下
You know, we should do that more.
因为我们不知道明天会发生什么
Because we never know what tomorrow's gonna bring.
好吧  如果你的百万富翁女朋友
Come on, all right, listen. If your billionaire girlfriend
不能说服你度过一段浪漫的假期
cannot whisk you away for a romantic holiday,
那这个世界真的很有问题了
then there really is something wrong with the world.
你说得很有道理
The lady has a point.
一向如此
The lady usually does.
这里有线索
Here's something.
弗莱德·罗伯茨  自由之子的成员之一
Fred Roberts, a known member of the Children of Liberty.
《外星人赦免法》签署之后
He sent hate mail to Stuart
他给斯图尔特发过仇恨邮件
after the Alien Amnesty Act was signed.
后来他因跟踪斯图尔特被捕并定罪
And then he was arrested and convicted for stalking him.
他上周刚被释放
He was released from prison last week.
我能获取的记录中没有释放地址
No release address listed in the records I have access to.
但是我觉得超查部可能有
But I think the DEO might have it.
你能缩小搜查范围吗
Any luck narrowing things down?
我在努力
I am working on it.
那你为什么在搜情人节礼物
Then why are you looking up Valentine's Day gifts?
我集中了85%的注意力
I am 85% focused,
相当于一支非常优秀的犯罪现场调查队
which is the equivalent to a very capable CSI team.
我只是还有一件重要的事需要处理
Now, I just have one other matter of importance to take care of,
处理完后  我保证会投入100%的精力
and once I do, I guarantee you 100% of my mind.
除非  你愿意帮我
Unless, of course, you'd like to help out?
这样的话  我能够早点结束一心多用
In which case, I could stop multitasking sooner.
-我确定  -我讨厌情人节
- I'm sure of it. - I hate Valentine's Day.
给你两分钟
Two minutes.
今天尼娅·纳尔邀请我参加一个情人节派对
Today, Nia Nal invited me to attend a Valentine's Day party.
她说"那就约好了"
She said, "It's a date."
但是  她的意图并不明确
Yet, her intentions were unclear.
"那就约好了"听起来很明确啊
"It's a date" does not sound unclear.
我从来没想过尼娅·纳尔这样优秀的人
It never occurred to me that someone as amazing as Nia Nal
会对我感兴趣
would be interested in me.
那么  更重要的问题是
Well, then, I guess the bigger question here is,
你希望如何
what do you want?
我希望她当我的情人
I want her to be my Valentine.
那就送她一份礼物  表达出这个意思
Well, then bring her a gift that expresses that.
勇敢的人想出的勇敢主意
What a bold idea from a very bold person,
艾丽克斯·丹弗斯
Alex Danvers.
过奖了
If only.
你身处危机之中
I mean, here you are, in the middle of a crisis,
-还能挤出时间思考人生  -是一心多用
- carving out time to figure out your life. - Multitasking.
好了  能不能赶紧搜查
Yes, can we get back to the search now, please?
没问题
Absolutely.
其实  针对新的两名受害者
In fact, I've just finished analyzing the police reports
我分析了警方报告
for the two additional victims.
除了受害者的死亡
It appears that beyond the deaths themselves,
受害者房子里的每件珠宝都被偷了
every piece of jewelry at their house was taken.
我知道发现第一个受害者的车辆
I understand the car where we found the first victim
参与了珠宝盗窃  那些珠宝也被拿走了
was involved in a jewel heist. Those jewels were also taken.
珠宝
Jewelry.
宝石和贵重金属对于这个外星人来说
Gems and precious metals could be an additional source
可能是另一种营养来源
of nutrition for this alien.
或者这对于那个外星人来说
Or potentially the alien requires the jewels
是他们星球的资源  无论如何
as a resource for its planet. In any event,
这都说明外星人在挑选受害者
it would suggest how this alien is choosing its victims.
如果它是步行  这会为我们提供搜索范围
If it's traveling on foot, that would give us a radius
以及要搜索的受害者特征
and a profile of victims for which to search by.
做一个三角测量  把地址发给我
Well, triangulate and send me the addresses.
荣恩  你还好吗
Hey, J'onn, is everything okay?
我有一个客户  她丈夫是外星事务部部长
I have a client whose husband, the Director of Alien Affairs,
似乎成了仇恨犯罪的受害者
might have been the victim of a hate crime.
我需要你帮我查一条潜在线索
I could use your help tracking down a potential lead
是卡拉帮我想出来的
Kara helped me come up with.
抱歉  我手上有未知外星人威胁
I'm sorry, I've got an unidentified alien threat
需要努力搜查
that I'm trying to track.
你可以打给布莱尼  他应该可以帮忙
But you should call Brainy, I'm sure he could help.
他很擅长一心多用
He's great at multitasking.
她把我转给了布莱尼
She re-directed me to Brainy.
我的说媒技术可真够烂的
So much for my matchmaking skills.
不过也不是什么好线索
Well, the lead was bad, anyway.
查不到罗伯茨的释放地址
There's no release address for Roberts
因为他已经回到了监狱
because he's already back in prison.
斯图尔特的电话记录
Stuart's phone records.
他与一个号码频繁通过电话
It appears he made consistent calls to a number
号码的主人是麦迪逊·辛克莱尔
belonging to Madison Sinclair.
尼娅写过一篇她的报道
Nia wrote an article about her.
她是个钻石经销商
She's a diamond broker.
她也投资过东城项目
One of the people who invested in the East City project.
过去几个月里  他似乎经常去
It appears he frequented a restaurant right by her house
她家旁边的一家餐厅
several times over the past couple of months.
今早又去了
And again this morning.
我认为这不是仇恨犯罪
I don't think this was a hate crime.
我觉得他出轨了
I think he's having an affair.
而且是在情人节当天
And on Valentine's Day.
我们还是需要保障他的安全
We still need to make sure he's safe.
屡次发生的外星人袭击让纳市市民
A series of alien attacks has the citizens of National City
深感不安
in a place of deep unrest.
-我是劳伦·哈雷上校  -我知道
- I'm Colonel Lauren Haley. - Yes, I'm aware.
解决外星威胁
...to combat the alien menaces.
在办公室见到我你似乎并不惊讶
You're not surprised to see me in your office.
我姓卢瑟  早就学会处变不惊了
I'm a Luthor. I've learned to expect the unexpected.
有什么事找我吗
Now, what can I help you with?
我是代表美国政府来的
I'm here on behalf of the President of the United States
想跟你签订一份政府合同
to offer you a government contract.
什么合同呢
For what purpose?
那个能够让人拥有超能力的药
People are terrified after the turmoil
给民众造成了巨大的恐慌与不安
created by that drug that gave humans super strength.
总统知道你的研究正在探索这个领域
The president understands your research is exploring this arena.
卢瑟女士  我们需要让美国军队
Ms. Luthor. We need to make the US military
与我们的外星对手一样强大
as powerful as our alien adversaries.
这并不是我开始这项研究的目标
This is not what I had in mind when I started my research.
纳欣诺市已进入高度警戒
...National City on high alert
有报道称未知外星人正在食用人类心脏
after reports of an unidentified alien feeding on human hearts.
有情报称死亡人数已达三人
Sources put the death toll at three already.
这正是我们需要你的原因
This is precisely why we need you.
我得走了
I need to go.
我邮件发你提议
I'll email you a proposal.
请考虑一下
Please think about it.
自由之子
Children of Liberty
要求立即释放本·洛克伍德
are calling for the immediate release of Ben Lockwood,
声称他是美国英雄  不是恐怖分子
stating that he is an American hero and not a terrorist.
于此同时  随着自由之子在城里掀起的新风波
Meanwhile, the Children of Liberty continue to grow their membership
成员队伍持续扩大
with new chapters arising throughout the city.
自由代表需要我们找到这个外星杀手
Agent Liberty needs us to find this alien killer.
我们以他的名义除掉杀手
Let us be the ones who kill it in his name.
就可以要求他被释放了
Then we can demand that he be set free.
录制结束
他在这里  那是他的车
He's here, that's his car.
我们要敲门吗
Should we knock?
万一他们...  就是...
Well, what if they're... You know...
我没法用X视线
Well, I can't use my X-ray vision.
辛克莱尔女士
Ms. Sinclair?
斯图尔特女士
Mr. Stuart?
他就在这里
He's right here.
我找到辛克莱尔女士了
I found Ms. Sinclair.
他的心脏不见了
His heart's missing.
不许动  把手举起来
Don't move! Hands in the air!
别动  站住
Freeze! Right there.
-所有人趴下  -等等  别开枪
- Everybody down! - Wait, hold your fire.
你们两个在这里干什么
What are you two doing here?
卡拉  你不用目睹这些的  走吧
Kara, you don't need to be seeing all of this. You should go.
我没事  犯罪现场我没少去
I'm fine. I've been to plenty of crime scenes,
给凯特克做报道
covering it for CatCo.
其实  我在这里
In fact, since I'm here,
说不定还能帮助调查
maybe I could help the investigation.
是她帮我们找线索找到这里来的
She is the one that helped find the lead that got us here.
你说你认为辛克莱尔女士
You said you thought Ms. Sinclair
被这个外星人盯上
was being targeted by this alien
是因为她是钻石代理商
because she was a diamond broker?
这是暗门
It's a hidden door.
重要发现  是吧  艾丽克斯
That's a good find, don't you think, Alex?
干得好  卡拉
Nice work, Kara.
这看上去像...  不清楚...
This looks like this could be, I don't know,
一种酸  甚至毒液
like, an acid, or maybe even venom,
因为我们找的是个外星人
given the alien we're looking for.
你能给它做放射性追踪吗  跟踪它
Could you run it for trace radioactivity? Perhaps to track it?
你怎么知道我们可以做这个
How did you know we could do that?
温  他经常拿他做的事吹牛
Winn, always bragging about how he did things.
当然了  是私底下
Off the record, of course.
能让布莱尼扫描吗
Couldn't you get Brainy to scan it?
可以
Yeah.
-多克斯特工  -是  丹弗斯局长
- Agent Dox. - Yes, Director Danvers?
那是音乐吗  你在哪
Is that music? Where are you?
我在我们讨论过的派对上
I am at the party we discussed.
叫做快乐时光
It was called for happy hour.
我还没跟那个
And I haven't yet conversed
之前我们提到的人说上话
with the person we spoke about earlier.
太疯狂了  别自言自语了  跳舞吧
Hey! This is my jam. Stop talking to yourself and dance.
而且我暂时很难脱身
Also, it might be difficult for me to extricate myself at the moment.
好吧  待着别动  我们过来
Okay, well, stay put. We're coming to you.
快点
Hurry.
你笑什么
Why are you smiling like that?
你说"我们"
You said "We."
当然了
Of course you did,
因为布莱尼在尼娅那里  荣要带我们飞过去
'cause Brainy's at Nia's and J'onn will fly us there.
安东尼·斯图尔特  外星事务部部长今日被杀
Anthony Stuart, the Director of Alien Affairs was murdered today.
外星事务部部长被外星人杀害
哈雷告诉你
You have an update from Haley
这个外星杀手的消息了吗
about this alien menace that killed him?
超查部正全力调查
The DEO's following all leads.
请提醒上校
Please remind the colonel
这正是我们的新法案如此重要的原因
this is why our new initiative is so important.
针对洛克伍德的抗议
And these Lockwood protests,
抗议者增加演变成抗议活动
变得越来越麻烦了
they're starting to become a nuisance.
我们该对他采取行动了
I think it's time we did something about him.
我今晚告诉您可选方案  长官
I'll bring you options tonight, sir.
布莱尼
Brainy?
你们看见他了吗
You guys see him?
没有
That's a negative.
艾丽克斯  你好吗  陌生人
Alex? How've you been, stranger?
我是贝卡  我们喝过酒的
It's Becca. We had drinks.
两次
Twice.
贝卡  天啊  抱歉我没给你打电话
Becca. Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry I never called you.
我...  我的生活...  太不可思议了
I... My life has just... It's been so crazy.
总有这种时候的  想喝一杯吗
It happens. Wanna grab a drink?
但是...  其实我得...
Um, you know what? Actually, I have to...
拜托  你不会连叙叙旧的时间都没有吧
Come on, don't tell me you don't have time to at least catch up.
去吧  叙叙旧  我们会找到他的
Go, go, catch up. We'll find him.
那好  行啊
Oh, yeah. Okay.
看样子她不需要姐妹了
It seems like she didn't need a wing-woman.
巴黎  我们来了
Paris, here we come.
正是时候
And not a moment too soon.
我听到了你战斗的号召
I heard your call to arms and,
我很为你骄傲  乔治
I'm really proud of you, George.
自由之子正在
The Children of Liberty are out there
搜索那个外星杀手
searching for that alien killer.
我不知道接下来该做什么
I'm just not sure what to do next.
这事你要公开解决
You gotta take care of it publicly.
人们必须知道是我们的功劳
People have to know that it's us.
我不知道我行不行
I don't know if I can.
乔治  我知道害怕的感觉  我们都知道
George, I know what it's like to be scared. All of us do.
但突然有个机会出现在你面前
But then, then an opportunity can present itself,
就像打开了开关
and like a switch,
你的整个世界就改变了
your whole world changes.
一切都清楚了
And you find clarity
你找到了目标
and focus, and strength
和你从未感知过的力量
like you've never known.
我需要你做的就是寻找那个机会
So what I need you to do is just look out for that opportunity
相信它
and trust it.
然后抓住这个机会
And you will take it.
他应该不在这里
I don't think he's here.
我就在这里
I am right here.
布莱尼  你在柜子里干什么
Brainy? What are you doing in the closet?
我刚躲开伊薇特  尼娅的室友
I just escaped Yvette, Nia's roommate.
显然  每首歌都令她疯狂
Apparently, every song is her jam.
你有样本吗
Do you have the samples?
这需要几分钟
This will take a few minutes.
你快去吧  我在这里等着
Well, you go. I'll stay here.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  过来坐
Yeah. Come sit.
你会渡过难关的
You're gonna get through this, you know.
别对自己那么严厉
Just go easy on yourself.
-你还有我在身边  -你不知道我有多感激
- And you have me. - You don't know how much I appreciate that.
只要
Just...
想想你母亲多爱你
think about how much your mother loved you.
想想她会希望你怎么做
And what she would've wanted for you.
努力实现她的愿望
And try to honor that.
她会希望我去运用梦境
She would want me to dream.
但是我姐
But my sister...
你不能让她阻止你接受命运的安排
You can't let her stop you from embracing your destiny.
我因为家庭隐藏了太久自己的真实身份
I hid who I was for far too long because of my family.
艾丽克斯一开始都不赞成我公开身份
Even Alex didn't think it was a good idea at first.
至少她现在知道真相并且支持你
At least now she knows everything and supports you.
实际上
Actually, um,
艾丽克斯不知道我是超女了
Alex doesn't know I'm Supergirl anymore.
为了保护她  她被消除了记忆
She had her mind wiped to protect her.
是的
Yeah.
但是我不能因此
But I can't let that stop
不去帮助需要帮助的人
me from helping the people that need my help
不去做做力所能及的好事
and doing the good that I can do.
你也可以做许多好事
And you could do a lot of good, too.
你现在是我家庭的一份子
You're part of my family now.
我们欢迎所有英雄
And all heroes are welcome.
跟我说说  联调局一定
So catch me up. The FBI must
对最近发生的事感到很头疼
be crazy with all the stuff that's happening.
还有领养的事  告诉我
And your adoption, tell me you
你是因为家里有小孩所以没联系我
have a kid and that's your excuse for not calling.
小孩  不  我还没有
A kid? Um, not yet.
对不起  你之前听上去很激动
Sorry. I know how excited you were about it.
是的  但是我大概突然断了念想
Yeah, I was. I, uh, guess I kind of dropped the ball.
那就重新拾起来
Then, pick it back up.
对不起  我的朋友需要我
Um, will you excuse me? My friends, they need me.
我很抱歉没有联系你
I really am sorry that I didn't call.
-你发现了什么  -没有辐射特征
- What did you find? - No radiation signature.
但是我在样本中发现了人类基因
But I did find human DNA in the sample.
-另一个受害者  -我觉得是的
- It's another victim? - I would assume.
联合基因索引系统有匹配  是帕梅拉·费勒
I found a match for the DNA in CODIS. Pamela Ferrer.
但纳市警局说  她还没有被报告失踪
But according to NCPD, she's yet to be reported as missing.
你有地址吗
Do you have an address?
克拉拉马里人是黄色的吗
Is a Klaramarian yellow?
我觉得他是想说有地址
I, uh, think that means yes.
是的  我当然有
Yes, obviously.
她的家其实就在几个街区之外
Her home is actually just a few blocks away.
我们应该准备行动
We should move out.
不  不  布莱尼和我会准备行动
No, no, no, no. Brainy and I will move out.
但是看你们在犯罪现场行动太有意思了
But that was so fun, seeing you in action at the crime scene.
卡拉  那会很危险
Kara, it could be dangerous.
把它想成顺风车
Think of it as a ride-along,
媒体跟去现场
the press tagging along
看政府如何保卫城市
to see how the government protects the city.
没错  我也一起去
Yeah, I'll come along, too.
-好的  一起行动就行  -没问题
- All right, well, just stick together. - Sure.
帕梅拉·费勒  你在吗
Pamela Ferrer, are you here?
我们是联调局
This is the FBI.
帕梅拉
Pamela?
我是帕梅拉·费勒  有什么问题吗
I'm Pamela Ferrer. Is there a problem?
是的  有重大的问题
Yes, there is very much a problem.
-布莱尼  -帕梅拉·费勒的基因
- Brainy! - Pamela Ferrer's DNA
和我们发现的外星毒液混合在一起
was commingled with the alien venom we found.
他们互相联系  无法分割
They were linked. Mandating contact.
她不可能还活着  更不用说没被伤害
She should not be alive, let alone unharmed.
情人节这天
With Valentine's Day,
我本该更专注于大脑思维
I must've been more preoccupied than I thought.
因为唯一合理的解释就是那条蛇
Because the only logical conclusion is that snake
没有变成我给你看的那个生物
didn't morph into that creature I showed you,
而是和那个女人结合了
but rather it merged with that woman.
-那个外星生物是共生体  -没错
- The alien is a symbiote? - Yes.
我98.9%肯定
I am 98.9% certain that
她是我们要找的怪物
she is the beast we're looking for.
我现在完全肯定
Make that 100%.
帕梅拉  我们想帮你
Pamela, we just want to help.
你身体里有东西让你这么做
There is something inside you making you do this.
-如果你试着反击  -反击
- If you try to fight it-- - Fight it?
我为什么要反击
Why would I fight it?
这是我感受过最强大的力量
This is the most powerful I have ever felt.
我的名字不是帕梅拉
And I am not Pamela.
我们是梅纳热里
We are Menagerie.
-我恨蛇  -卡拉快跑
- I hate snakes. - Kara, run!
卡拉  不
Kara! No!
回来吧
Come.
-你没事吧  -完全没事  她没咬中
- Are you okay? - It's totally fine. She missed me.
我没事  告诉过你了  它只扯破了外衣
I'm fine. I told you. It just ripped my jacket.
我发现了这些  装满了珠宝和钱财
I found these. Full of jewels and money.
看起来帕梅拉·费勒是个珠宝大盗
It would appear Pamela Ferrer is a jewel thief.
很可能是第一个受害者的同伙
Likely accomplice to our first victim.
好的  所以心脏是
Okay, so the hearts were
共生体喜欢的  而珠宝是她喜欢的
for the symbiote and the jewels were for her.
现在我们知道了共生体的人形态
Now that we know the symbiote's human counterpart,
我们就可以追踪她
we can track her.
好的  布莱尼  你回超查部
Okay, Brainy, you get back to the DEO,
用人脸识别系统找她
use your facial algorithm to find her and then
我送卡拉回家后过去找你
I'll meet you back there after I take Kara home.
我告诉你  我没事
I told you, I'm fine.
我比你想的要坚强
I am tougher than you think I am.
听着  如果你有什么闪失
Look, I would never forgive myself
我不会原谅我自己
if something happened to you.
卡拉  你是这世上对我来说
Kara, you're the most important person
最重要的人
in the world to me.
我最看重的就是你的安全
Hey, your safety is my number one priority.
没有事情比那更重要
Nothing comes before that.
你知道吗  你说的没错
Uh, you know what? You're right.
我的确感觉有点害怕
I do feel a little shaky.
-我带她回家  -好的
- I'll take her home. - Okay.
谢谢  荣恩
Thanks, J'onn.
好的  打扫干净这里
All right, sweep this place.
留下巡逻队  她回来了就向我报告
Leave a patrol. If she comes back, I wanna know about it.
政府想要和我合作
The government wants to partner with me
一起研究如何让人类拥有超能力
in my research into making humans super.
莉娜  我知道你的研究对你意味重大
Lena, I know how much your research means to you,
所以我才无法理解
which is why I can't fathom why
你为什么想要和政府共享研究成果
you would want to share it with the government.
我以为你支持我的工作
I thought you supported my work.
听着  我知道我说过能理解
Look, I know that I said that I understand
你所涉足的道德灰色地带
this moral gray area that you're treading on.
但如果你和政府分享你的研究
But if you share your research with the government,
他们就会把它军事化
they're gonna militarize it.
谁知道那会造成什么样的混乱呢
And who knows what kind of chaos that can create.
我知道我说过会努力
I know I said that I'd try
理解你的观点
to understand your point of view.
但我不知道在这件事上能不能做到
But I don't know if I can on this one.
你是说  原谅我
Are you saying that forgiving me
以及我们再试试看是个错误吗
and us trying again was a mistake?
不不不  我...  不不不  没有错误
No, no, no, I'm... No, no, no. There's no mistakes.
不  我爱你
No, I love you.
你也爱我
And you love me.
但我也了解你  我知道你不是那种人
But I also know you and I know that you're better than this.
我不会允许你看低我
I will not allow you to judge me
我可是在用科学追求人类进步
for my using my science for the betterment of humanity.
有道理  好吧
That's fair. Okay.
你是对的  我也不想看低你
You're right and I don't want to judge.
但坦率说  我从来没有
But to be straightforward, I am never
打算同意你
going to agree with you
去和政府分享你的研究
sharing your research with the government.
我觉得那会毁了我们
And I think that that could destroy us.
你可能是对的
You're probably right.
我觉得你该走了
I think you should leave.
所以就这样吗
So that's it then?
总是不可避免  不是吗
It was always inevitable, wasn't it?
弗兰克  停车
Frank, stop the car.
孩子  你没事吧
Girl, are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
做了个噩梦而已
Just a bad dream.
我更喜欢你整夜不睡觉的时候
I liked it better when you stayed up all night.
帮我清理一下吧  我不是一个人在工作
Now help me clean this up. I'm not doing this work by myself.
我们试过  但我没法和艾丽克斯一起工作
We tried, but I can't work with Alex.
以超女或卡拉的身份都不行
Not as Supergirl or as Kara.
她吓了一跳  那并不意味着她不喜欢
She got spooked. That doesn't mean she didn't enjoy
在那之前和你一起工作
working with you before that.
在她以为我被那条蛇咬了的时候
When she thought I was bit by that snake...
我在她眼睛里看到过无数次那种样子
I've seen that look in her eyes a million times.
那是爱  但也是深深的恐惧
It's love, but it's also deep fear.
那就是爱的深度
That's the depth of love
是我们对最在乎的人才拥有的
we have for the people we care about the most.
但问题是爱会阻碍某人
But it's a problem when that love stops someone
去追求自己想要的东西
from going after what they want for themselves.
你觉得艾丽克斯为你这么做了吗
And you think that's what Alex does for you?
还记得她说过她觉得自己的生活停滞不前
Remember when she said she felt like her life was on pause
并且不知道原因吗
and she didn't know why?
她搞不清楚是什么阻碍了她
And she couldn't figure out what was holding her back.
是我  是我阻碍了她
It's me. I'm what's holding her back.
今年夏天她做得那么好
She was doing so well this summer,
她又开始约会了  她在推进收养计划
she was dating again, she was moving forward with the adoption,
然后那颗氪石炸弹砸下来了
and then that Kryptonite bomb hit
她放弃了一切来照顾我
and she dropped everything to take care of me.
听着  别为此自责
Look, please don't blame yourself for that.
那不是你的错
That wasn't your fault.
艾丽克斯没去追求她的梦想
Alex isn't pursuing her dreams
是因为她太过专注于保护我
because she's so focused on protecting me.
现在她的记忆被抹去了
And now that her mind is wiped,
她不记得超女是她的妹妹
now that she doesn't remember her sister is Supergirl,
她终于能解脱了
she's finally free of that.
但我作为卡拉和她一起工作就不行了
But not if I work with her as Kara.
我觉得这次记忆消除对我们家庭的伤害
Oh, man. I feel like this mind wipe has hurt our family
比我们能预料到的方式还要多
in so many more ways than we could ever foresee.
或许这对她来说就是最好的
Maybe this is what's best for her.
艾丽克斯想要一个孩子和一个伴侣
Alex wants a baby, she wants a partner
现在她终于能自由地追求了
and now she's finally free to pursue that.
我不会和她一起工作  但...
And no, I won't get to work with her, but...
我还是拥有我姐姐
I'll still have my sister.
我还是拥有你
And I'll still have you.
找到了
Got it!
我的天  这些特工都死了  提醒是对的
Oh, my God, all these agents are dead. The tip was right.
分头行动  看看那个外星人还在不在
Spread out. See if that alien's still here.
我希望它已经不在了
I hope it's not still here.
所有战利品都不见了  他们什么都拿走了
All the loot is gone. They took everything.
这个星球上的人一直都这么做
That's what humans on this planet always do.
心脏协会的化妆舞会
Heart Association's Masquerade Ball.
是时候开始重建我的净值了
It's time for me to start rebuilding my net worth.
她要去市中心的爱心协会化妆舞会
She's heading to the Heart Association Masquerade Ball downtown.
我会把录像发过去
I'll send the video.
我会把这个发给我父亲的网络
I'll send this out to my father's networks
这样他们就可以去那里杀了那东西
so they can get there and kill that thing.
好的
Okay.
我一直都喜欢戴钻石表的男人
I've always had a thing for a man with a diamond watch.
喜欢你的项链
Love your necklace.
所有人  现在都出去
Hey! Every human, get out now!
我们要杀了那个外星人
We're gonna kill that alien.
吼别人很不礼貌
You know it's rude to yell at people.
你发现了她
You found her.
不是我  是自由之子
Not me. The Children of Liberty.
他们刚刚上传了梅纳热里的镜头
They just uploaded footage of Menagerie
在纳欣诺市爱心协会化妆舞会上
at the National City Heart Association Masquerade Ball,
这真是太讽刺了
which I must say is ironic.
让一支队伍在车上和我碰面
Have a team meet me at the van.
这座城市最不需要的就是活生生的屠杀
Last thing this city needs is a live slaughter.
孩子  那个舞会要开始了
Girl, that Ball is right around the corner.
这地方真的很差劲了
This neighborhood has really gone to the pits.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
快走  快走
Move! Move!
自由之子  放下武器
Children of Liberty, stand down.
放下武器
Stand down!
梅纳热里
Menagerie.
你应该有别的乐趣  而不是保护那些人
You should have better taste than to protect those people.
我保护每个人
I protect everyone.
真的是你的损失
Your loss. Literally.
-真不可思议  -我在梦里见过它
- That was amazing! - I saw it in a dream.
可能本该也见过那个
Probably should've seen that, too.
你可以去里面帮艾丽克斯  我来对付她
Alex could use your help inside. I'll deal with her.
无论你释放出多少共生兽
However many symbeasts you unleash,
我都有能力阻止它们
I have the power to stop them.
你们氪星人以为自己足够强大
You Kryptonians think you're so powerful on your own.
你对于在一个团队中所产生的
You know nothing of the symbioses
互利共生关系一无所知
that comes from being part of a team.
-她在那里  -我们抓住她吧
- There she is. - Let's get her.
别杀她  她已失去能力  我可以制服她
Don't kill her. She's disabled. I can bring her in.
不
No!
我们杀掉了怪物  保护了这个城市的人民
We protected the humans of this city by killing a monster.
对
Yeah!
即使是超女都做不到这点
Not even Supergirl could do that.
-自由  -自由
- Liberty! - Liberty!
-自由  -局长
- Liberty! - Director?
这些警官会处理之后的事
These officers will take it from here.
上校
Colonel?
她体内的外星人已死
The alien inside her was killed,
所以她不再是个威胁
so she no longer poses a threat.
总统想把她作为例子
The president wants her made an example of.
把她关进监狱  而不是什么秘密行动基地
Sent to prison, instead of some black ops site
没人会再看见她
where no one can see her.
联调局需要向媒体发表篇声明吗
Should the FBI be making a statement to the press?
让他们知道自由之子
Let them know that the Children of Liberty
真的让这次行动更艰难
actually made this whole thing harder?
我们花更多时间保护他们而不是去阻止她
We spent more time protecting them than stopping her.
那我们就得把功劳归于超女
Well, then we'd have to give credit to Supergirl.
你觉得这会让那群人消停些吗
Oh, you think that would make things better with that crowd?
这应该靠我们自己  局长  不用任何帮助
It should've been us, Director. Without any assist.
超女不是敌人  上校
Supergirl is not the enemy, Colonel.
但是我们必须靠自己处理这些外星人了
Yeah, but we have to start handling these aliens on our own.
明天我会告诉你总统的计划
I'll update you tomorrow on the president's plan to get us there.
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我以为我们解决了自由之子
I thought we were done with the Children of Liberty.
他们将胜利归功于己  但是真相会大白于天下
They took credit for this win but the truth will prevail.
很遗憾你不能与你姐姐在一起
I'm sorry you can't be down there with your sister.
我们仍是同一队伍
We're still on the same team,
只是离的远些
just from a distance.
衣服不错
Nice suit.
这是我妈妈的
It was my mother's.
你是对的
And you were right, you know.
今晚我为她而战
I honored her by fighting tonight.
你是知道你可能会死的
You do realize you could've gotten yourself killed.
-当然  -那就好
- Absolutely. - Okay.
有很多
Yeah, there was, um,
有很多事我都能预见的
there was a lot that I should've seen coming.
你的超能力让你有成为伟大英雄的潜力
Your powers give you the potential to be a great hero.
但你仍然需要学习控制超能力
But you still have to learn how to control them.
好好练习
So get to work.
那
So...
-布莱尼  -正是
- Brainy. - Yes, it is.
看看他给我带了什么
Look what he brought me.
严格地讲
Uh, yes, well, technically,
我没有给伊薇特那个爱心盒子
I did give Yvette that heart-shaped box.
-那不是给她的  -没关系  布莱尼
- It wasn't actually meant for her. - It's fine, Brainy.
我不需要你的巧克力
I don't need chocolates from you.
我需要你帮我训练
What I need is for you to help me train.
尝尝这个椰子味的
Oh, try the coconut.
最好吃的
It's the best one.
看起来所有情人节糖果
So, it seems all Valentine's candy
在午夜过后
goes to 80% off
都打八折了
after midnight.
你不用买的
Whoa! You shouldn't have.
但我很高兴你买了
But I'm glad you did.
我
Hey, I, uh...
我想为之前的事道歉
I wanted to apologize about before.
当我以为我看到你受伤时
I just felt like this trigger went off
我觉得我就不受控了
when I thought I saw you get hurt.
我想你肯定很害怕
I'm sure it was scary.
但那只是割破了你的上衣
But all it did was just tear your jacket.
听着  你知道这是你我第一次
And look, I know this is the first time that you and I
经历刚刚那种情况
have been in a situation like this before,
但是我第一反应就是
but I think my go-to response is just
保护我觉得有困难的人
protect anybody that I see that's in trouble.
不管他们到底想不想我帮
Whether they want me to or not.
但我意识到
But I realize that, you know,
我常常会忘记
the person that I most often
保护我自己
forget to protect is me.
相信我  我不会再跟着
Well, trust me, I won't be tagging along
去犯罪现场调查了
for any crime scene investigations anymore.
不不不  这不是你的错
No, no, no, it's not you.
我要开始相信人们可以保护自己
I need to start trusting that people can also protect themselves.
这样我就可以
You know, that way I can just
把精力集中在我想做的事情上
start focusing my energy into the things that I want.
现在  我终于准备好了
And... I'm finally ready.
很好
Well, good.
因为我帮你要到了
'Cause I got that girl
尼娅派对上那个女孩的电话
from Nia's party's number for you.
贝卡  这是她的名字
Becca, that's her name.
我会打给她的
But... I'm gonna call her.
然后我要开始
And then I'm just gonna start
去做所有我想做的事情
pushing play on all the things that I wanna do.
我要去填完收养文件
And I'm gonna finish that adoption portfolio
提交表单
and submit the forms.
我对此表示祝贺
I can cheers to that.
祝贺祝贺
Oh, yes.
我加入
I'm in.
找到什么了吗
Did you find something?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
《爱国者法案》只保护人类生命不受恐怖主义伤害
The Patriot Act only protects human life from acts of terrorism.
洛克伍德不能被起诉
Lockwood can't be charged under it.
让白宫法律顾问马上签字
Get the White House counsel to sign off now.
纳欣诺市
男子中央监狱
我不怕
I wasn't afraid.
今天是个好日子
Today is a good day.
自由之子保护了纳市市民
The Children of Liberty protected the citizens of National City
不受残暴的外星人伤害  美国总统
against a murderous alien, and the President of the United States
终于理解了我们的唯一要务
finally understands that our one mission
就是保护人类
is to safeguard human life.
我在此  作为一个自由的人
So I stand before you now, a free man,
准备继续服务这个伟大的国家
ready to continue to serve this great nation.
谢谢你的支持
Thank you for your support.
给你的信
Letter for you.
-谁寄的  -曼彻斯特·布莱克
- From who? - Manchester Black.